怎么迟到啦
Why are you late?
你是不会喜欢我的答案
You're not going to like the answer.
我早就知道了
I already know the answer.
我没赶上公车
I missed the bus.
那当然咯
I don't doubt it.
布莱家附近没有公车站
No bus stops near Brad's.
你在他家过夜  闹钟没响
You spent the night, the alarm didn't work
响了也当没听见
or maybe it did.
我没有跟他上床
I didn't sleep with him.
美女  事情才没这么简单
Girl, either there's something
只不过是没赶上公车
I missed the bus!
要么是你有问题
There's something either very wrong with you
要么是他有问题
or something very wrong with him.
他没有问题
There's nothing wrong with him.
马琳  我得走了
Melanie, I gotta go.
你在忽悠我的  对吧
You're lying, aren't you?
我才不会忽悠你
I wouldn't lie to you.
早上好呀  小朋友们
Good morning, guys!
早上好  丽贝卡老师
Good morning, Miss Rebecca!
-大家都到齐了吗  -是的
- Everybody's in their seats? - Yes.
好的
Okay.
仙蒂
Sydney,
告诉大家你这个周末都干什么啦
why don't you tell us what you did this weekend?
来吧  仙蒂
Come on, Sydney.
你可不是个害羞的孩子哦
We know you're not shy.
为什么总让我们说
How come we always have to tell you what we did,
而你却从来不说呢
and you never tell us what you did?
好吧
Okay.
我这个周末过的棒极了
I had a really great weekend.
但你们不可以告诉马琳老师哦  好吗
But you can't tell Miss Melanie, okay?
你做什么啦
What did you do?
我交了个新朋友
I made a new friend.
交新朋友总是很开心的  对吗
It's so much fun to make new friends, isn't it?
是呀  是呀
Yeah. Yeah.
告诉你爸妈你那位新朋友了吗
Did you tell your mom and dad about your new friend?
当然咯
Absolutely.
任何事都不可以瞒着爸妈
You should never keep anything from your parents.
我说完我的...
And I told mine
C-A- L-
H-E   The
H-E, The!
我们认识那个字  The
We know that word. "The."
女性  29岁
Twenty-nine-year old female.
在一个月前首次癫痫发作
First seizure one month ago.
失去语言能力  只能像婴儿一样嘟囔
Lost the ability to speak. Babbled like a baby.
阶段性智力退化
Progressive deterioration of mental status.
看见没
You see that?
就因为这拐杖  大家都把我当病人
They all assume I'm a patient because of this cane.
那就像我们一样穿上白大褂
So put on a white coat like the rest of us.
我更不想让人知道我是医生
I don't want them to think I'm a doctor.
难怪你会让上面这么头疼
You see where the administration might have a problem with that attitude?
没有人会要一个有病的医生
People don't want a sick doctor.
当然咯  我也不要健康的病人
That's fair enough. I don't like healthy patients.
这名二十九岁女病人
The 29-year old female
就喜欢她不会说话
The one who can't talk? I like that part.
她是我的表妹
She's my cousin.
你表妹肯定不会喜欢我的诊断
And your cousin doesn't like the diagnosis.
我也不会
I wouldn't either.
得的是脑瘤  命不久矣  无聊透顶
Brain tumor. She's going to die. Boring.
你这位诊断专家还真是名不虚传
No wonder you're such a renowned diagnostician.
闭着眼睛就能作诊断
You don't need to actually know anything to figure out what's wrong.
你才是肿瘤专家
You're the oncologist.
我不过是个小小的传染病医生
I'm just a lowly infectious disease guy.
那是  你不过是个赤脚郎中
Yes. Just a simple country doctor.
她这年龄患脑瘤可能性很小
Brain tumors at her age are highly unlikely.
她才二十九岁  患什么都不太可能
She's 29. Whatever she's got is highly unlikely.
三种最常见脑瘤的蛋白标记都呈阴性
The protein markers for the three most prevalent brain cancers came up negative.
那是保健室
That's an H.M.O. Lab.
跟高中实验室一样烂
Might as well have sent it to a high school kid with a chemistry set.
没有家族病史
No family history.
你叔不是死于癌症的吗
I thought your uncle died of cancer.
另一边的表妹  没有环境致病因素
Other side. No environmental factors.
你不知道而已
That you know of.
且对放疗没反应
And she's not responding to radiation treatment.
说这么半天没说到一个重点
None of which is even close to dispositive.
仅让我产生一个疑问
All it does is raise one question:
你表妹竟然去保健室看病
Your cousin goes to an H.M.O.?
拜托  干嘛把乐趣都留给验尸官呢
Come on. Why leave all the fun for the coroner?
如果不找些事情给他们做
What's the point of putting together a team
那还要他们来干嘛
if you're not gonna use them?
你手下有三位能力超群的医生
You've got three overqualified doctors
成天百无聊赖
working for you, getting bored.
是脑损
It's a lesion.
在地图上
And the big green thing
碧蓝中的一点鲜绿
in the middle of the bigger blue thing on a map...
是小岛
is an island.
还以为你要语出惊人呢
I was hoping for something a bit more creative.
作诊断前不是该先了解病人吗
Shouldn't we be speaking to the patient before we start diagnosing?
-她是医生吗  -不是  可是
- Is she a doctor? - No, but-
所有人都撒谎
Everybody lies.
豪斯医生从不和病人打交道
Dr. House doesn't like dealing with patients.
治疗病人不正是我们做医生的原因吗
Isn't treating patients why we became doctors?
你错了  治疗疾病才是我们做医生的原因
No. Treating illnesses is why we became doctors.
治疗病人是让医生痛苦不堪的原因
Treating patients is what makes most doctors miserable.
所以  你从医学治疗中除去人性
So you're trying to eliminate the humanity from the practice of medicine?
只要不和他们接触
If we don't talk to them,
他们就无法撒谎
they can't lie to us,
我们也不必对他们撒谎
and we can't lie to them.
人性总被高估
Humanity's overrated.
这不是肿瘤
I don't think it's a tumor.
在医学院第一年就知道
First year medical school
听到马蹄声  要想到马而不是斑马
if you hear hoofbeats, you think horses, not zebras.
你还停留在大学一年级吗
Are you in first year medical school?
不是  首先造影扫描没有异常
No. First of all, there's nothing on the CAT scan.
第二  倘若这真是一匹马
Second of all, if this is a horse,
任何庸医都能诊断出来
then her kindly family doctor in Trenton makes the obvious diagnosis,
她也不会来了
and it never gets near this office.
伙计们  开始鉴别诊断啊
Differential diagnosis, people.
若非肿瘤  还有什么可能
If it's not a tumor, what are the suspects?
她怎么会不能说话
Why couldn't she talk?
动脉瘤  中风或是其他缺血性综合征
Aneurysm, stroke or some other ischemic syndrome.
-做核磁共振成像  -是克雅病
- Get her a contrast M.R.I. - Creutzfeldt-Jakob disease?
-疯牛病  -疯斑马病
- Mad cow? - Mad zebra.
韦尼克脑病
Wernicke's encephalopathy.
不对  血液中硫胺水平正常
No. Blood thiamine level was normal.
那破烂保健室搞砸了所有血检
The lab in Trenton could have screwed up the blood tests.
人们闯祸都想尽办法掩饰
I assume it's a corollary if"people lie" that "people screw up."
重做血测
Redraw the blood tests
尽快安排核磁共振成像
and get her scheduled for that contrast M.R.I. ASAP.
看看这到底是什么斑马
Let's find out what kind of zebra we're treating here.
放射科  请呼叫
Radiology, please call the page.
我二十分钟前就在办公室等你
I was expecting you in my office 20 minutes ago.
真的吗  那就怪了
Really? Well, that's odd
我二十分钟前压根就没想去你办公室
because I had no intention of being in your office 20 minutes ago.
你以为我们没什么可谈吗
You think we have nothing to talk about?
正是如此  想不出要跟你说什么
No. I just can't think of anything I'd be interested in.
-我是你的衣食父母  -我是终身职位
- I sign your paychecks. - I have tenure.
想抢我的拐杖不让我走吗
Are you gonna grab my cane now, stop me from leaving?
我才不跟你一般见识
That would be juvenile.
如果你玩忽职守我还是可以解雇你
I can still fire you if you're not doing your job.
我每天按时上下班
I'm here from 9:00 to 5:00.
-你基本没有工作量  -经济不景气啊
- Your billings are practically nonexistent. - Rough year.
你无视会诊
You ignore requests for consults.
我回了  打错电话而已
I call back. Sometimes I misdial.
你已经落下六年的门诊任务
You're six years behind on your obligations to the clinic.
看吧  早说过咱俩无话可谈
See? I was right. This doesn't interest me.
六年  每年三周
Six years times three weeks
你欠下四个月的门诊时间
you owe me better than four months.
五点了  该回家了
It's 5:00. I'm going home.
回家干嘛
To what?
行啊你
Nice.
我至今仍没有解雇你的唯一理由
Look, Dr. House, the only reason why I don't fire you...
就是你的声誉对医院还有价值
is because your reputation is still worth something to this hospital.
很好  在不解雇我这一方面
Excellent. We have a point of agreement
咱总算达成共识
you're not gonna fire me.
如果你继续懒散下去
Your reputation won't last
你那名声会化为乌有
if you don't do your job.
门诊也是工作的一部分
The clinic is part of your job.
我希望你能尽职
I want you to do your job.
伟大的"哲人"贾斯汀曾说过
But, as the philosophers Jagger once said,
"世事并不总遂人愿"
"You can't always get what you want."
你不是我的医生  你是豪斯医生吗
You're not my doctor. Are you Dr. House?
幸亏不是  我是奇斯医生
Thankfully, no. I'm Dr. Chase.
豪斯医生是诊断部门的负责人
Dr. House is the head of diagnostic medicine.
他事务繁忙
He's very busy,
但他对你的病例尤其上心
but he has taken a keen interest in your case.
我们将对比剂注入静脉
We inject gadolinium into a vein.
它会自由遍布大脑
It distributes itself throughout your brain
做磁共振成像造影剂
and acts as a contrast material for the magnetic resonance imager.
总之  要把你的大脑变成圣诞树
Basically, whatever's in your head lights up like a Christmas tree.
-可能会感觉头晕  -卡梅隆医生
- It might make you feel a little light-headed. - Dr. Cameron.
抱歉  打断一下  出问题了
I'm sorry. I have to stop you. There is a problem.
你竟敢没收我的权限
You pulled my authorization!
没错  这么激动干嘛
Yes. Why are you yelling?
没有核磁共振成像  影像检查和实验检测
No M.R.I.'s, no imaging studies, no labs.
你还不能打长途电话
You also can't make long distance phone calls.
真想炒我就冲我来
If you're going to fire me, have the guts to face me.
你还不能用复印机  你还在嚷嚷啊
Or photocopies. You're still yelling.
我很生气  你竟拿病人生命开玩笑
I'm angry! You're risking a patient's life.
这两件事没关系吧
I assume those are two separate points.
你不尊重我  让我难堪
You showed me disrespect. You embarrassed me.
我还在这一天  你就没有权利...
And as long as I work here, you have no legal-
你是想吓唬我吗
Is the yelling designed to scare me?
我到现在还不知道该怕些什么
Because I'm not sure what it is I'm supposed to be scared of.
还要接着嚷吗  一点都不吓人
More yelling? That's not scary.
如果说你要打我  那才可怕
That you're going to hurt me? That's scary.
可我跑得绝对比你快
But I'm pretty sure I can outrun you.
还是你那位"哲人"贾斯汀说得对
Oh, I looked into that philosopher you quoted-Jagger.
"世事并不总遂人愿"
And you're right, you can't always get what you want.
但事实上  "倘若努力"
But as it turns out, "If you try sometimes,
"总能得到自己想要的"
you get what you need."
就是说  你想让我治疗病人
So, because you want me to treat patients,
却要反其道而行吗
you're not letting me treat patients?
我要的是  你做好本职工作
I need you to do your job.
做核磁共振  她投降了
Do the M.R.I. She folded.
我每周得做四小时门诊
I've got to do four hours a week in this clinic
直到补回我所落下任务
until I make up the time I've missed.
整整两千零五十四个小时
2054. I'll be caught up in 2054.
你最好深爱着你这表妹
You better love this cousin a whole lot.
好的  丽贝卡
All right, Rebecca,
你可能感觉幽闭
I know you may feel a little claustrophobic in there,
但请别乱动
but we need you to remain still.
好的  开始了
Okay, we're going to begin.
我不舒服
I don't feel so good.
没关系  放松点
It's all right. Just try to relax.
丽贝卡
Rebecca?
-把她弄出来  -可能只是睡着了
- Get her out of there. - Oh, she probably fell asleep.
-她累了  -三十秒前她还有幽闭恐惧
- She's exhausted. - She was claustrophobic 30 seconds ago.
她不是睡着  快把她弄出来
She's not sleeping. We gotta get her out of there.
还有一分钟就好了
It'll just be another minute.
如果是对比剂过敏  马上会没命
If she's having an allergic reaction to the gadolinium, she'll be dead in two minutes.
-托住颈部  -好的
- Hold her neck.  - All right.
面色苍白
Oh, she's ashen.
呼吸停止了  肾上腺素  0.5毫克
She's not breathing.  Epi, .5.
加油
Come on.
机械通气不行
I can't ventilate.
水肿太严重
Too much edema.
-气管切开器械包  -来了
- Where's the surgical airway kit?  - Yep. Coming.
厉害
Good call.
今天晚些时候会把插管取出
We'll get that tube out of your throat later today.
现在先好好休息
Just get some rest for now, okay?
早说了  不能相信任何人
Told you.  You can't trust people.
她可能知道自己对比剂过敏
She probably knew she was allergic to gadolinium.
发现是个让人帮她开喉的好方法
Figured it was an easy way to get someone to cut a hole in her throat.
不能做脑部扫描  只好靠千言万语了
Can't get a picture. Gonna have to get a thousand words.
你真想让我们跟病人聊天  套病史吗
You actually want me to talk to the patient, get a history?
需要了解
We need to know
触发炎症反应的遗传和环境因素
if there's some genetic or environmental cause that's triggering an inflammatory response.
你不是说所有人都撒谎吗
I thought everybody lied.
真相恰恰始于谎言
Truth begins in lies.
好好想想吧
Think about it.
他又在胡言乱语  对吧
That doesn't mean anything, does it?
下午12:52
12:52 p.m.
豪斯医生签到  请记上
Dr. House checks in. Please write that down.
有线电视在哪
Do you have cable TV here somewhere?
《总院故事》八分钟后开始
General Hospital starts in eight minutes.
没电视  但有病人
No TV, but we've got patients.
你就不能自己去发阿司匹林吗
Can't you give out the aspirin yourself?
把书面工作交给我
I'll do paperwork.
我保证第一个病例就很有意思
I made sure your first case was an interesting one.
咳嗽好不起来
Cough just won't go away?
鼻涕的颜色古怪
Runny nose looks a funny color?
病人背部痉挛
Patient admitted complaining of back spasms.
听起来像新英格兰医学杂志上的病例
Oh? I think I read about something like that in the New England Journal of Medicine.
病人是橙色的
Patient is orange.
-颜色吗  -不是  我说水果
- The color? -No, the fruit.
你是说黄色  那是黄疸
You mean yellow. It's jaundice.
是橙色
I mean orange.
好吧  橙到什么份上  大概只是...
Well, how orange? It's probably
一号诊室
Exam room one.
卡恩医生  请到儿科
Dr. Kahn, you're needed in pediatrics.
我打高尔夫时  球鞋卡住了
I was playing golf and my cleats got stuck.
有点疼  不过我没停
It hurt a little, but I kept playing.
第二天早上  我疼得站不起来
The next morning, I could barely stand up.
你在笑  说明我病情不重
Well, you're smiling, so I take it that means this isn't serious.
那是什么  你干吗
What's that? What are you doing?
止痛药
Painkillers.
因为你的腿
Oh, for you. For your leg.
错了  是因为药片嚼起来香
No, 'cause they're yummy.
想来一片吗  能让你的背舒服点
You want one? Make your back feel better.
不幸的是  你的问题远比表象严重
Unfortunately, you have a deeper problem.
你老婆有外遇
Your wife is having an affair.
-什么  -你都变橘子啦  蠢人
- What? - You're orange, you moron.
你没注意到是一回事
It's one thing for you not to notice,
要是连你老婆都不知道自己老公变色了
but if your wife hasn't picked up on the fact that her husband has changed colors,
说明她就没拿正眼看你
she's just not paying attention.
顺便问你一句
By the way,
你是不是狂吃胡萝卜和维生素药丸
do you consume just a ridiculous amount of carrots and megadose vitamins?
胡罗卜让你变黄   烟酸让你变红
Carrots turn you yellow, the niacin turns you red.
不信的话自己拿调色盘试试
Find some finger paint and do the math.
再找个好律师
And get a good lawyer.
深呼吸
Deep breath.
好冰啊
It's cold.
他一直在用气雾吸入器吗
He's been using his inhaler?
最近几天没有  他才十岁
Not in the past few days. He's, um, only 10.
不想给孩子用太多强效药
I worry about children taking such strong medicine so frequently.
你的腿怎么了
What happened to your leg?
我想医生也考虑过药物强度
Your doctor probably was concerned about the strength of the medicine too.
权衡过呼吸停止和用药危险的利弊
She probably weighed that danger against the danger of not breathing.
氧气对于青春期前的青少年尤为重要
Oxygen is so important during those prepubescent years.
你说对吗
Don't you think?
好吧  我想是没人告诉过你哮喘是什么
Okay, I'm gonna assume nobody has ever told you what asthma is.
或者别人说的时候  你心不在焉
Or if they have, you had other things on your mind.
你孩子气管里的细胞被刺激
A stimulant triggers cells in your child's airways...
分泌出的物质导致气管发炎并收缩
to release substances that inflame the air passages and cause them to contract.
黏液分泌增加  细胞层开始脱落
Mucus production increases, the cell lining starts to shed.
但类固醇
But the steroids
类固醇终止炎症反应
The steroids stop the inflammation.
类似情况发生次数越多
The more often this happens-
然后呢   类似情况发生越多  会怎样
What? The more often this happens, what?
算了  你要是不信类固醇
Forget it. If you don't trust steroids,
也没必要信医生
you shouldn't trust doctors.
我母亲四年前去世
My mother passed away four years ago.
她得了心脏病
She had a heart attack,
我父亲在工地上弄伤背
and my father broke his back doing construction-
是豪斯  紧急状况  对不起
It's House. It's urgent. I'm sorry.
你就不能敲门吗
You couldn't have knocked?
类固醇  用类固醇  大剂量强的松
Steroids. Give her steroids. High doses of prednisone.
你在寻找证据支持脑血管炎的诊断
You're looking for support for a diagnosis of cerebral vasculitis?
脑血管炎极其罕见  尤其在她这年纪
Inflammation of blood vessels in the brain is awfully rare, especially for someone her age.
肿瘤同样罕见  红细胞沉降率升高
So is a tumor. Her sed rate is elevated.
少幅上升而已
Mildly.
或许说明很多问题  或者无关紧要
That could mean anything. Or nothing.
对  我知道不该断定这是血管炎
Yeah, I know. I have no reason to think that it's vasculitis.
除非  有这可能性
Except that it could be.
倘若是脑血管炎  症状完全符合
If the blood vessels are inflamed, that's gonna look exactly like
还有核磁共振结果
what we saw on the M.R.I. From Trenton County,
颅内压会导致神经学症状
and the pressure is gonna cause neurological symptoms.
没有活检  不能妄下诊断
We can't diagnose that without a biopsy.
当然可以
Yes, we can.
开始治疗
We treat her.
情况好转  则证明我们是对的
If she gets better, we know we're right.
-要是错了呢  -那就有新发现
- And if we're wrong? - Then we learn something else.
为什么用类固醇
Why steroids?
只是治疗的一部分
Just part of your treatment.
没什么人来看你
You haven't had many visitors.
-没有男友吗  -才约会过三次
- No boyfriend? - Three dates.
换成他从早吐到晚  我也不愿来
I wouldn't have stood by him if he were vomiting all day.
同事呢  总有好朋友吧
What about work? You must have friends from work.
我喜欢的人都只有五岁
Pretty much everybody I like is five years old.
护士说不做放疗了
The nurse said you're stopping my radiation.
我们在尝试不同的治疗
We're just trying some alternative medication.
你家是哪里的
So where's your family from then?
类固醇和放疗毫不相干
Steroids aren't an alternative to radiation.
现在还无法确诊
The tests weren't really conclusive.
我们在针对血管炎治疗
We're treating you for vasculitis.
是一种脑部血管炎症
It's the inflammation of blood vessels in the brain.
不是肿瘤吗
It's not a tumor?
我得的不是肿瘤
I don't have a tumor?
你不该告诉她的  那不过是猜测
You shouldn't have told her the truth. It's a long shot guess.
如果豪斯是对的  没关系
If House is right, no harm.
如果他错了  我给了一个濒死之人几天希望
If he's wrong, I've given a dying woman a couple days' hope.
虚无的希望
False hope.
如果可以的话  我也愿意给真的
If there was any other type available, I would have given her that.
你干嘛闻比利的裤子
Why are you smelling Billy's pants?
-我没有  -你是在闻啊
- I'm not. - Looked like you were.
我在闻地板
I was smelling the floor.
这里有宠物吗
Do you have any pets in this class?
没  以前有过一只沙鼠
No. But we used to have a gerbil,
不过被卡利的书压死了
but Carly L. dropped a book on it.
真不小心
Careless.
你想要闻闻它吗
Do you need to smell it?
不用  我找的是霉菌
No. I'm smelling for mold.
不用闻那个
I don't need to smell it.
你还可以闻闻我们的鹦鹉
You could smell our parrot.
你不是说这里没宠物了吗
You said you didn't have any pets in this class.
可鹦鹉是鸟啊
A parrot is a bird.
听着  杰克逊不是孩子他爹
Listen, Jackson's not the father-
鹦鹉是鹦鹉热的主要传染源
Parrots are the primary source of psittacosis.
和鹦鹉没有关系
It's not the parrot.
鹦鹉热解释了神经问题和神经学并发症
And psittacosis can lead to nerve problems and neurological complications.
-一个班里多少学生  -二十个
- How many kids were in the class? - Twenty.
-几个病假在家  -没有  不过
- How many are home sick? - None, but-
没人生病  你觉得五岁小孩
None. But you figured that five-year-olds
会比老师更懂得清理小鸟卫生吗
are more serious about bird hygiene than their teacher?
-去她家查过了吗  -她住在特伦顿
- Have you been through her home? - She lives in Trenton.
我明天问她拿钥匙
I can go up to her room tomorrow morning, ask her for the key.
警察突击犯罪现场  会先问过嫌犯吗
Would the police call for permission before dropping by to check out a crime scene?
那不是犯罪现场
It's not a crime scene.
据我所知  她在地下室偷造冰毒
As far as I know, she's running a meth lab out of her basement.
她是个幼儿园老师
She's a kindergarten teacher.
要是我是幼儿园学生  我也信她
And if I were a kindergarten student I would trust her implicitly.
好吧  举个例子
Okay. I'll give you a "for instance."
那边  给你做三明治的太太
The lady back there... who made your egg salad sandwich-
有注意到她眼神呆滞吗
Her eyes look glassy. Did you notice that?
医院规定  生病不可上班
Now, hospital policy is to stay home if you're sick.
但倘若你连每小时八块的事都干
But if you're making $8.00 an hour,
那么你一定很缺这八块钱
then you kind of need the $8.00 an hour, right?
还有  洗手间里的牌子上写着
And the sign in the bathroom says
雇员如厕后必须洗手
that employees must wash after using the facilities,
但我想  用袖子擦鼻涕的人
but I figure that somebody who wipes snot on a sleeve
也不会讲究卫生
isn't hyperconcerned about sanitary conditions.
我现在问你  我还吃她做的东西吗
So what do you think- should I trust her?
我要你去她家查污染源  垃圾  用药
I want you to check the patient's home for contaminants, garbage, medication.
我才不会擅闯民宅呢
I can't just break into someone's house.
你当年不也干过这档子事吗
Isn't that how you got into the Felkers' home?
我知道了
Yeah, I know.
虽说法庭记录是保密的
Court records are sealed.
你才十六岁  这事的确不光彩
You were 16. It was a stupid mistake.
而你那体育老师又是个大嘴巴
But your old gym teacher has a big mouth.
该写信谢谢他
Should write a thank-you note.
我还该谢他
I should thank him?
我总会用到个懂得小偷小摸的人
I needed somebody around here with street smarts.
得知道什么时候被人摆布  也知道如何摆布别人
Okay? Who knows when they're being conned, knows how to con.
我该告你去
I should sue you.
你才不会告自己的衣食父母
Pretty sure you can't sue somebody for wrongful hiring.
要是你因为我不违法
But I'm pretty sure I can sue
而解雇我的话  我绝对会告你
if you fire me for not breaking into some lady's house.
做研究呢  人类太奇妙了
Doing research. People are fascinating, aren't they?
为什么给阿德用类固醇
Why are you giving Adler steroids?
因为她是我的病人
Because she's my patient.
用药不正是治疗的一部分嘛
That's what you do with patients- you give them medicine.
你不能单凭猜测用药
You don't prescribe medicine based on guesses.
只有塔斯克基和门格勒才这么做
At least we don't since Tuskegee and Mengele.
你竟然把我说成纳粹医生  行啊
You're comparing me to a Nazi? Nice.
我现在就停药
I'm stopping the treatment.
-她是我的病人  -这是我的医院
- She's my patient. - It's my hospital.
我没让病情恶化
I did not get her sick.
我没拿她做实验
She is not an experiment.
我做的是合理的猜测
I have a legitimate theory about what's wrong with her.
但缺乏证依据
With no proof.
从来就没有依据
There's never any proof.
同样的症状  一百医生会有一百种诊断
Five different doctors come up with five different diagnoses based on the same evidence.
可你连一个症状都没有
You don't have any evidence.
没有人能什么事都知道
And nobody knows anything, huh?
那你凭什么就知道自己是对的
Then how is it you always think you're right?
我只知道反其道而行是错的
I don't. I just find it hard to operate on the opposite assumption.
为什么你那么如此惧怕错误
And why are you so afraid of making a mistake?
因为我是医生  掌握的是人命
Because I'm a doctor. Because when we make mistakes, people die.
别这样
Oh, come on.
过去人们可尊重瘸子了
People used to have more respect for cripples, you know.
其实没有
They didn't really.
-感觉怎么样  -好多了  谢谢
- So how you feeling? - Much better, thanks.
你是豪斯医生吗  我还以为他是男的
Are you Dr. House? I thought he was a he, but-
不是我
No.
慢慢吃  别吃太多
Don't eat too much, too fast.
替我谢谢他
Thank him for me.
好的
Right.
老大  是不是还要我中止治疗呢
Should I discontinue the treatment, boss?
走狗屎运罢了
You got lucky.
很酷吧
Cool, huh?
好的  再来一次
Okay, once again.
很好
Good.
我什么时候才能见见豪斯医生啊
Am I ever gonna meet Dr. House?
你可能会在电影院或大巴撞见他
Well, you might run into him at the movies or on the bus.
他是个好人吗
Is he a good man?
他是个好医生
He's a good doctor.
不能医德兼修的吗
Can you be one without the other?
医生不是都很关心病人的吗
Don't you have to care about people?
关心的确能成为行医的动力
Caring is a good motivator.
但有别的东西更吸引他
He's found something else.
两边都感觉到了吗
Feel this, both sides?
用力  使劲  很好
Okay, squeeze. Harder. All right.
他是你的朋友  对吧
He's your friend, huh?
是的
Yeah.
他关心你吗
Does he care about you?
-我想是吧  -你感觉不到吗
- I think so. - You don't know?
正如豪斯常说的  所有人都撒谎
As Dr. House likes to say, "Everybody lies."
关键不在乎说什么  而在于做什么
It's not what people say. It's what they do.
没错  他关心我
Yeah. He cares about me.
我看不见了
I can't see.
我看不...见了
I can't... see.
紧急呼叫
A little help in here!
你现在会感到胸部疼痛
Your chest will be sore for a while.
必需用除颤仪才能让你恢复心跳
We needed to shock you to get your heart going.
你能把卡片按时间顺序排列吗
Okay, can you arrange these to tell a story?
她做不到
She couldn't put them in order.
会不会是发病时大脑缺氧造成的
Could the damage have been caused by a lack of oxygen during her seizure?
不对  五分钟后她做相同测试
No. I gave her the same test five minutes later.
完成的不错
She did just fine.
同语言能力一样  精神状态呈间歇变化
The altered mental status is intermittent, just like the verbal skills.
现在怎样
So what now?
从最近的症状来看
Given the latest symptoms,
脑干已受影响
it's clearly growing deeper into the brain stem.
很快  她将失去行走能力
Soon, she won't be able to walk.
并伴有永久性失明
She'll go blind permanently, and
随后呼吸中枢衰竭
then the respiratory center will fail.
我们还剩多长时间
How long do we have?
如果是肿瘤  还有一两个月
If it's a tumor, we're talking a month or two.
感染的话  就几周
If it's infectious, a few weeks.
如果是血管
If it's vascular,
那就只剩一周左右
that'll probably be fastest of all. Maybe a week.
停止所有的治疗
We're gonna stop all treatment.
我仍认为是肿瘤
I still think it's a tumor.
我们应该继续采用放疗
I think we should go back to the radiation.
放疗根本不起效果
She didn't respond to the radiation.
可能放疗效果在
Well, maybe we didn't see the effect
施用类固醇后才显现出来
until after we started steroids.
不是肿瘤
No, it's not a tumor.
类固醇起到某种作用  只是不知道是什么
Those steroids did something. I just don't know what.
难道我们就这样睁睁看着她死去吗
So we're just gonna do nothing? We're just gonna watch her die?
没错  我们就看着她死去
Yeah, we're gonna watch her die.
更确切地说  是要看她死得有多快
Specifically, we're gonna watch how fast she's dying.
你也说过每种病死亡时间都不同
You just told us- each diagnosis has its own time frame.
看她什么时候死  就知道她得的是什么病
When we see how fast it's killing her, we'll know what it is.
到那时我们就无能为力了
And by then, maybe there's nothing we can do about it.
我们一定还能做些什么
There's got to be something we can do.
总不能眼睁睁看着她死掉
Something better than watching her die.
我就没有办法了
Well, I got nothing.
你有吗
How about you?
混蛋
Bastard.
对了  卡梅隆  我想借你几小时
Oh, Cameron. I need you for a couple of hours.
什么事
What's up?
擅自闯入别人家时
When you break into someone's house,
-最好带个白人女性  -是阿德家吗
- it's better to have a white chick with you. - Adler's house?
为什么不问她拿钥匙
Why don't we just ask her for her keys?
据说她在地下室偷造冰毒
For all we know, she'll be running a meth lab out of her basement.
我常常犯困
I'm tired a lot.
还有别的病症
Any other reason why you
让你认为自己患有慢性疲劳综合症吗
think you might have chronic fatigue syndrome?
容易犯困不正是疲劳症吗
It's kind of the definition, isn't it?
更可能是衰老
It's kind of the definition of getting older.
上个月有过几次头痛  还有低烧
I had a couple headaches last month, a mild fever.
有时失眠  难以集中注意力
Sometimes I can't sleep, and I have trouble concentrating.
显然你没上网查过这个病之前都好好的
Apparently not while researching this stuff on the Internet.
另一个可能是纤维肌炎
I was thinking it also might be fibromyalgia.
绝妙的诊断
Excellent diagnosis.
有药可治吗
Is there anything for that?
你别说  还真有
You know, I think there just might be.
给我36维科丁  再帮我兑一块钱
I need 36 Vicodin and change for a dollar.
送到二号病室
Exam room two.
豪斯痛恨矫揉造作
House doesn't believe in pretense.
他认为人生苦短
Figures life's too short and too painful.
所以他总是有话直说
So he just says what he thinks.
垃圾没什么特别的
Nothing interesting in the garbage.
"有话直说"
"I say what I think" is
换句话说就是  "他是混蛋"
just another way of saying "I'm an assho"-
如果想证明你的医术高明
Well, if you wanted to be judged for your medical prowess only,
那咱就不用擅闯民宅了
maybe you shouldn't have broken into someone's home.
当时我才十六岁
I was 16.
不知道有没有寄生虫
Don't know about ticks,
但她家狗肯定有跳蚤
but her dog's definitely got fleas.
我十七岁时私闯民宅  但没留下案底
I managed to make it to 17 without a criminal record.
是吗
Yeah?
那你肯定不在我那区长大的
Well, you obviously didn't grow up in my neighborhood.
那是  你偷面包
That's right. You stole a loaf
是给你家里人吃的  对吧
of bread to feed your starving family. Right?
你总这样偷吃人家东西的吗
You always eat during break-ins?
还要我像对待她家DVD机
Am I supposed to respect their
那样小心地对待她家食物啊
food more than I respect their DVD players?
-要吃点吗  -不了
- You want some? - No.
你要等她死后才吃东西啊
You gonna go hungry until she dies?
-才不是  -知道吗
- No. - You know what?
黑人经受几个世纪奴隶制折磨
After centuries of slavery,
还有几十年的民权斗争
decades of civil rights marches...
而我仍然过着修道士的生活
and, more significantly, living like a monk,
各科成绩都从没低过四分
never getting less than a 4.0 G.P.A.,
却靠擅闯民宅得到一份好工作
you don't think it's kind of disgusting I get
换做是你  不会觉得恶心吗
one of the top jobs in the country because I'm a delinquent?
等我吃完了  再看看地毯下面有什么
We'll eat, then we'll tear up the carpet.
你是霍普金斯大学毕业的吗
You went to Hopkins, right?
对
Yep.
那你的学校比我的好
So you went to a better school than I did.
成绩也比我的好
You got better grades than I did.
那你是怎么会被录用的
So how did you get the job?
该不会你在酒吧捅过什么人吧
You stab a guy in a bar fight?
什么都找不到
Nothing.
不是肿瘤  病情恶化速度太快
It's not a tumor. She's getting worse too fast.
-她都站不起来了  -没有毒品或药物吗
- She can't stand up. - No toxins? No medications?
找不到能解释她病症的东西
Nothing that would explain these symptoms.
有家族性的神经疾病吗
Family history of neurological problems?
光从她家内衣抽屉  我看不出家族病史
Not that I could tell from her underwear drawer.
你说"找不到能解释她病症的东西"
You said "Nothing that would explain these symptoms."
那你找到的都是些什么
What did you find that doesn't explain these symptoms?
威尔森医生是骗你的
Dr. Wilson convinced you to treat this patient under false pretenses.
阿德不是他表妹
Adler's not his cousin.
荒唐  你可以去问她啊
That's ridiculous. You can ask her yourself.
-能回到...  -她根本就不是犹太人
- Can we get ba... - She's not Jewish.
蕾切·阿德不是犹太人吗
Rachel Adler's not Jewish?
在她公寓找到了火腿
I had ham at her apartment.
福曼医生  很多犹太人有非犹太的亲戚
Dr. Foreman, a lot of Jews have non-Jewish relatives,
很多犹太人也不吃犹太洁食
and most of us don't keep kosher.
高中生不懂犹太习俗还能原谅
I can see getting through high school
可你是堂堂医学院的毕业生
without learning a thing about Jews, but medical school?
即便她是犹太人
Okay, maybe she's Jewish,
她也绝不会是你表妹
But she's definitely not your cousin.
是吗  你这是...
Really? This guy is-
你甚至不知道她叫什么
You don't even know her name.
你叫她蕾切  可她分明叫丽贝卡
You called her Rachel. Her name is Rebecca.
没错  她是叫丽贝卡
Yes. Yes, her name is Rebecca.
小名是蕾切
I-I call her Rachel.
-你这白痴  -听我说  他...
- You idiot! - Listen, he's-
没说你  说他
Not you. Him.
你刚说你什么也没有找到
You said you didn't find anything.
我找到的东西都...
Everything I found was in my
-你找到火腿了  -那又怎样
- You found ham. - So?
找到火腿就是说有猪肉
Where there's ham, there's pork.
有猪肉  就说明可能是脑囊尾蚴病
Where there's pork, there's neurocysticercosis.
绦虫  你是说她大脑里有猪肉绦虫
Tapeworm? You think she's got a worm in her brain?
完全吻合
It fits.
可以在大脑里寄生好几年
Could have been living there for years. Never occurred to me that-
每天数百万的人都在食用火腿
Millions of people eat ham every day.
这个可能性微乎其微
It's quite a leap to think that's she's got a tapeworm.
神经专家  脑囊尾蚴病患者
Okay, Mr. Neurologist, what happens
施用类固醇后  会出现什么反应
when you give steroids to a person who has a tapeworm?
病情稍作好转后  急转直下
They- They get a little better, and-and then they get worse.
跟丽贝卡·阿德一样
Just like Rebecca Adler did.
典型病例  如果烹调猪肉时间不够
In a typical case, if you don't cook pork well enough,
绦虫幼体会进入消化系统
you digest live tapeworm larvae.
它们身体长有小钩
They've got these little hooks,
能吸附在肠壁上
they grab onto your bowel,
寄生  成长  繁殖
they live, they grow up, they reproduce.
怎么会繁殖  病灶只有一个
Reproduce? There's only one lesion,
且绝不在肠内
and it's nowhere near her bowel.
因为这并非典型病例
That's because this is not a typical case.
绦虫一天内能产下两万到三万只卵
Tapeworm can produce 20,000 to 30,000 eggs a day.
-知道卵都去哪了吗  -排出体外
- Guess where they go?  - Out.
总有漏网之鱼
Not all of them.
与幼虫不同
Unlike the larvae, the egg can pass right
虫卵能穿过肠壁到血液
through the walls of the intestines into the bloodstream.
-血液通向哪里呢  -全身各处
- And where does the bloodstream go? - Everywhere.
只要虫卵健康
As long as it's healthy,
免疫系统不会产生排斥
the immune system doesn't even know it's there.
寄生虫通过分泌特殊物质逃过免疫监测
The worm builds a wall, uses secretions to
并控制体液流动
shut down the body's immune response and control fluid flow.
整个过程配合得天衣无缝
It's really very beautiful.
只要绦虫健康她就安全  怎么办
As long as it's healthy. So what do we do?
叫兽医将这寄生虫治好吗
Call a vet, nurse the little guy back to health?
太迟了  它已经快死了
It's too late for that. It's dying.
如果它死掉  寄生虫就不能
And as it dies, this parasite
抵御宿主的免疫系统监测
loses the ability to control the host's defenses.
这时免疫系统重新恢复免疫  吞噬蠕虫
The immune system wakes up, attacks the worm,
一切都开始沸腾
and everything starts to swell.
对大脑是严重的伤害
And that is very bad for the brain.
但也不能排除其他可能性
It could still be a hundred other things.
嗜伊红血球数量正常
The eosinophil count was normal.
数量不正常的病例只占的30%
It's only abnormal in 30% of cases.
这说明不了什么
Proving nothing.
到现在你还不懂吗
No, no, no, no. It...don't you see?
这与病情相符  解释了一切
It fits. It's perfect. It explains everything.
却证明不了什么
But it proves nothing.
-我能通过治疗来证明  -你不行
- I can prove it by treating it. - No, you can't.
刚才和她谈过了  她不愿再接受任何治疗
I was just with her.She doesn't want any more treatments.
也不愿再去做任何检验  只想回家等死
She doesn't want any more experiments.She wants to go home and die.
请你出去一下好吗
Would you excuse us, please?
我是豪斯医生
I'm Dr. House.
很高兴见到你
It's good to meet you.
你这个白痴
You're being an idiot.
你的大脑里有绦虫
You have a tapeworm in your brain.
情况不妙
It's not pleasant,
如果不做治疗  你活不过这周末
but if we don't do anything,you'll be dead by the weekend.
你看到虫子了吗
Have you actually seen the worm?
等你康复  就拿我的文凭给你看
When you're all better,I'll show you my diplomas.
你之前还认为我得的是血管炎呢
You were sure I had vasculitis too.
现在我无法走路  还穿上尿布
Now I can't walk and I'm wearing a diaper.
这个治疗能又能让我怎样
What's this treatment gonna do for me?
现在说的不仅是治疗  而是治愈
I'm not talking about a treatment.I'm talking about a cure.
可能我错了  你宁可去死
But because I might be wrong,you want to die.
你是怎么瘸的
What made you a cripple?
我得了血管梗塞
I had an infarction.
是心脏病吗
A heart attack?
是由于血流受阻而引起的疾病
It's what happens when blood flow is obstructed.
梗塞在心脏就是心脏病
If it's in the heart,it's a heart attack.
在肺部是肺动脉栓塞
If it's in the lungs, it's a pulmonary embolism.
在脑部是脑中风  我的血栓在大腿肌肉
If it's in the brain, it's a stroke.I had it in my thigh muscles.
他们都无计可施了吗
Wasn't there something they could do?
如果他们诊断正确  方法还有很多
There was plenty they could do,if they'd made the right diagnosis.
但疼痛是唯一症状
But the only symptom was pain.
极少数人出现肌坏死
Not many people get to experience muscle death.
你想过死吗
Did you think you were dying?
本想一死了之
I hoped I was dying.
所以现在你躲在办公室里  不见病人
So you hide in your office,refuse to see patients...
因为你讨厌人们的眼光
because you don't like the way people look at you.
感觉被命运玩弄
You feel cheated by life,
所以要报复这个世界
so now you're gonna get even with the world.
但你却让我与病魔抗争
But you want me to fight this.
为什么
Why?
凭什么你觉得我比你好
What makes you think I'm so much better than you?
怎么了  你害怕会变成我吗
What, you're scared you'll turn into me?
我只想死得有尊严
I just want to die with a little dignity.
根本就没这回事
There's no such thing.
我们的身体都会崩溃
Our bodies break down.
有的人在九十岁
Sometimes when we're 90.
有的人在出生以前
Sometimes before we're even born.
生命就是这样
But it always happens,
毫无尊严可言
and there's never any dignity in it.
我不管你能不能走路  看东西
I don't care if you can walk,see,
擦自己屁股
wipe your own ass.
生命永远都是丑陋的  永远都是
It's always ugly. Always.
只能带着尊严活着  不能带着尊严去死
We can live with dignity.We can't die with it.
还是不接受治疗
No treatment.
也许可以申请一份法院令
Maybe we can get a court order,uh,
否决她的愿望
override her wishes,
说她没有作决定的能力
claim she doesn't have the capacity to make this decision.
但她可以
But she does.
不过我们可以说
But we could claim that
疾病使她精神错乱  对吧
the illness made her mentally incompetent, right?
-这样就皆大欢喜  -别费力气了
- A pretty common result.  - That didn't happen here.
他不会这么做的
He's not gonna do it.
对豪斯来说她已经不只是单纯的病例
She's notjust a file to him anymore.
他尊重她
He respects her.
尊重她  你就让她去死吗
So because you respect her,you're going to let her die?
我已经作出诊断  没我什么事了
I solved the case.My work is done.
病人总是要证明
Patients always want proof.
我们又不是造汽车的
We're not making cars here.
才不会提供担保
We don't give guarantees.
我想我们能证明
I think we can prove it's a worm.
非入侵性检查  绝对安全
It's noninvasive. It's safe.
我也不太确定  但是
I'm not completely sure, but...
得  得  你到底想说什么
Yeah, yeah, yeah.What's the damn idea?
你在X光片中见过虫子吗
Have you ever seen a worm under an X-ray?
一种常规  古老  无对比度
A regular, old, no-contrast,
上百年科技的X光片
hundred-year-old-technology X-ray?
虫子的X光片看起来像是猎枪子弹
They light up like shotgun pellets,
跟核磁共振成像一样
just like on a contrast M.R.I.
可我们已做过CT透视
Which is the same thing as a CT scan,
什么都看不见
which we did, which proved nothing.
虫胞密度和脑脊髓液密度相近
The worm's cyst is the same density as the cerebrospinal fluid.
所以在大脑中找不到绦虫
We're not gonna see anything in her head.
可奇斯说对了
But Chase is right.
他是对的  可以做X光
He's right. We should X-ray her.
可这次不是大脑  而是她的腿
But we don't X-ray her brain. We X-ray her leg.
虫子喜欢大腿肌
Worms love thigh muscle.
如果她的大脑里有虫子
If she's got one in her head,
大腿中肯定也有
I guarantee you there's one in her leg.
别动  丽贝卡
Hold still, Rebecca.
这里
This here...
是一只幼虫
is a worm larva.
我腿里有虫子  就是说大脑里也有吗
So, if it's in my leg,it's in my brain?
你不是想要证明吗
Are you looking for a guarantee?
这就是  它可能已经在那住六年了
It's there.Probably been there six to ten years.
-还有更多吗  -很有可能
- Do I have more?  - Probably.
这是个好消息
It's good news.
-现在该怎么办  -让你好起来
- What do we do now?  - Now we get you better.
阿苯达唑
Albendazole.
就两片药
Two pills?
是的  每天饭后  持续服用一个月
Yeah. Every day,for at least a month, with a meal.
-就两片药吗  -没错
- Two pills?  - Yeah.
可能出现的不良反应有
Possible side effects include
腹痛  呕吐  头痛  眩晕  发烧
abdominal pain, nausea, headaches, dizziness, fever...
还有脱发
and hair loss.
即使你出现以上所有不良反应
We'll probably make you keep taking the pills
还是要坚持吃药
even if you get every one of those.
你为什么雇我
Why did you hire me?
这重要吗
Does it matter?
很难为不尊重自己的人工作
Kinda hard to work for a guy who doesn't respect you.
-为什么  -这是你的口头禅吗
- Why?  - Is that rhetorical?
不是  只是奇怪你会不知道答案
No. It just seems that way 'cause you can't think of an answer.
你真的在乎我的想法吗
Does it make a difference what I think?
我是个混蛋
I'm a jerk.
重要的是你自己的想法
The only thing that matters is what you think.
你能胜任这份工作吗
Can you do the job?
你雇福曼  是因为他有少年犯罪史
You hired a black guy because he had a juvenile record.
才不是
No.
这不是种族问题
It wasn't a racial thing.
我看到的不是个黑人
I didn't see a black guy.
而是一名医生
I just saw a doctor...
兼有少年犯罪史
with a juvenile record.
我雇奇斯  因为他爹老烦我
I hired Chase 'cause his dad made a phone call.
我雇你
I hired you...
因为你美艳动人
because you are extremely pretty.
你竟然只图我的美色
You hired me to get into my pants?
你这么奇怪干嘛
I can't believe that that would shock you.
我可没这么说
It's also not what I said.
错了  我雇你  是因为你养眼
No, I hired you because you look good.
就像门廊里的花瓶
It's like having a nice piece of art in the lobby.
我是我们班里的尖子
I was in the top of my class.
但并非名列前茅
But not the top.
我还在梅奥诊所做过实习医生
I did an internship at the Mayo Clinic.
没错  你的确在众求职者中促类拔萃
Yeah. You were a very good applicant.
但并非最好的
But not the best.
这让你很沮丧吗  真的
Would that upset you? Really?
我雇你是  看在你的天生丽质
To think that you were hired because of some genetic gift of beauty
而非天资聪颖  所以你很不快吗
instead of some genetic gift of intelligence?
我是几经辛苦才得到这份工作的
I worked very hard to get where I am.
但你不需要
But you didn't have to.
人们总是选择用最小努力
People choose the paths that gain them the greatest rewards
换取最大的回报
for the least amount of effort.
这是人之常情
That's a law of nature,
而你却反其道而行
and you defied it.
这才是我看中你的原因
That's why I hired you.
你大可以嫁给一个富翁  或者做名模
You could have married rich. You could have been a model.
你只要稍微卖弄姿色
You could havejust shown up and
就能得到想要的东西
people would have given you stuff.
很多东西
Lots of stuff.
可你却没有  你抛开自己容貌上的优势
But you didn't. You worked your stunning little ass off.
我是不是该感到荣幸啊
Am I supposed to be flattered?
美女不会进医学院
Gorgeous women do not go to medical school...
除非美丽的外表下藏着一颗受伤的心
unless they're as damaged as they are beautiful.
你被家人虐待过吗
Were you abused by a family member?
-没有  -被强奸过吗
- No.  - Sexually assaulted?
没有
No!
反正你的心是受伤的  对吧
But you are damaged, aren't you?
我得走了
I have to go.
我跟踪她
I followed her.
我脑子里满是那医生的话
I couldn't stop thinking about what that doctor said.
告诉过你别听他的  他是个白痴
I told you not to listen to him.He's an idiot.
我变橙色了
I was orange!
我不想知道你发现了什么
I don't want to know what you found out.
你不关心吗
You don't care?
我只是你的医生
I'm your doctor.
我很感激你为我以及医院做的一切
You've been good to me and good to this hospital.
我当然关心
Of course I care.
但是我不知该如何收场
But I don't see how this conversation can end well for me.
不管你的老婆有没有外遇
Neither your wife is having an affair,or she's not having an affair,
你来我这都是想要我开除他
and you have come here because you rightly think I should fire him.
可是我做不到  即便你花钱
But I can't.Even if it costs me your money.
这个混蛋是我们最好的医生
The son of a bitch is the best doctor we have.
感觉好些了吗
Feeling any better?
挺好的
I can't complain.
你知道的  医院里有明文规定
As you know, the hospital has certain rules.
而我们喜欢无视那些规定
And as you also know, we tend to ignore them.
但是这的确有些明目张胆
But I think this one's gonna be a little obvious
除非你帮忙
unless we get your help.
如果谁问起
If anyone asks,
你就说你有十一个女儿和五个儿子
you have 11 daughters and five sons.
看是谁来了
Hi! Look who's here!
我想死你们了
It's so good to see you guys.I missed you.
是给我的吗
Is this for me?
太漂亮了
It's beautiful.
我爱你们
Oh, I love you guys.
我想当面感谢豪斯医生
I wanted to thank Dr. House,
但他没再来看我了
but he never visited again.
他治好了你  你却没有治好他
He cured you. You didn't cure him.
好吧  我要亲亲你们每一个人
Okay, I want a hug and a kiss
快上来吧
from every single one of you! Get up here right now!
-那里  -夹住了
- There.  - Hold on.
扩散了
She's converted.
你说她是你表妹
You said she was your cousin.
为什么骗我
Why would you lie?
那样你才会接这病例
It got you to take the case.
你欺骗一位朋友拯救一个陌生人
You lied to a friend to save a stranger.
你不觉得有点不够意思吗
You don't think that's kind of screwed up?
你就没骗过我
You've never lied to me?
我从不撒谎
I never lie.
那是
Oh. Right.
-我们为什么这样做  -因为我们是医生
- Why do we do this?  - Because we're doctors.
手中掌握的是人命
If we make mistakes, people die.
豪斯医生
Dr. House?
你有病人
You have a patient.
他是来继续开药的
He says he needs a refill.
有一块钱硬币吗
Got change for a dollar?